SOFTWARE ENGINEER · FRONT END DEVELOPER

Summary

Third year student pursuing a BS in Informatics/Software Development at SUNY Albany.

Love to learn through practical projects and experience. Big fan of JetBrains and Linux. Always trying to customize to find the most optimal environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools.

Experience

Albany Medical Center

Albany, NY

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSOCIATE

Nov. 2022 - Jan. 2023

- · Helped patients with scheduling appointments, insurance, and other administrative tasks in the Pediatric Surgery unit.
- Answered phones and directed calls to the appropriate hospital department.
- Assisted with the preparation, storage, and retrieval of patient charts and medical records.
- Daily use of Microsoft Office, including Word, Excel, Outlook, and Teams.

GrubHub New York City, NY

DELIVERY DRIVER

Aug. 2021 - Nov. 2022

- Delivered food to customers in a timely manner.
- Communicated with customers to ensure they received their food and were satisfied with their order.
- Used GPS to navigate to customer locations.
- · Handled cashless transactions and maintained accurate records of earnings.
- Adhering to all traffic laws and regulations while driving.
- Maintained the cleanliness and safety of the delivery vehicle.
- Daily use of Google Maps and Google Sheets.

Northwell Health Long Island, NY

PATIENT SERVICES Dec. 2020 - Aug. 2021

- · Transported patients to and from exam rooms and their vehicles in an outpatient hospital environment.
- Cleaned and sanitized exam rooms and equipment between patients. Stocked exam rooms with supplies.
- Entered patient information into the electronic medical record system, with an emphasis on HIPAA compliance.

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2020 Arctic Code Vault Contributer, GitHub Archive Program

Online

Education

State University of New York at Albany

Albany, New York

B.S. IN INFORMATICS/SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Expected May 2024)

• Recieved Presidential Scholarship which is awarded to promising students.